yourself.
Oh, get there.
THE CITY IS REBELLING AGAINST
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT JUST LIKE
IN CHICAGO.
PORTLAND PD WON'T KEEP FEDERAL
AGENTS SAFE EITHER.
THEY ACTUALLY SLAPPED THEM WITH
A ZONING VIOLATION FOR BOARDING
UP THEIR BUILDING'S WINDOWS SO
ANTIFA CAN'T SEE INSIDE.
THEY BELIEVE WOMEN HAVE A RIGHT
TO PRIVACY, JUST NOT ICE.
AN ICE FACILITY WAS JUST SHOT UP
IN DALLAS AND NOW CARTELS HAVE
BOUNTIES ON THEIR HEADS.
THEY'RE MAKING PLANS TO AMBUSH
THEM AND TO KILL THEM.
WE HAVE SPECIFIC OFFICERS AND
AGENTS THAT HAVE BOUNTIES THAT
HAVE BEEN PUT OUT ON THEIR HEADS.
IT'S BEEN $2,000 TO KIDNAP THEM,
$10,000 TO KILL THEM.
WE'RE TRYING TO PROTECT THE
COUNTRY FROM CARTELS AND THEY'RE
SAYING WE'RE AT WAR WITH AMERICANS
AND CHRISTIE NOEM SHOULD BE CHARGED
WITH WAR CRIMES.